Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
If...
If I could have another chance...
Hospital.
My hand is all right...
My feet too...
Not a scratch on my chest
where I got stabbed.
Was it a dream?
You woke up?
I...
I'm the chief of the Surveillance Team
in Hunter's Association. Woo Jinchul.
I'm Kang Taeshik.
Surveillance Team...
Why are you here to see me?
Well.
I'll call the doctor over first.
What?
I've been unconscious for three days?
What about Joohee and Mr. Song?
Are they okay?
They're fine. But...
Hunter Song Chiyul lost an arm.
He might choose to retire.
As for Hunter Lee Joohee.
she's suffered significant
psychological trauma
and is currently undergoing treatment.
Judging from her condition.
it's uncertain whether she can
continue to work as a hunter.
Only six people came back alive
from the double dungeon.
The hunter profession
inherently comes with risks.
such a casualty is still rare.
And for some reason.
when we received reports
from the survivors
and got there with members
of the White Tiger Guild.
they only found you lying there.
There were no traces
of any temple or statues.
But how...
Hard to believe. isn't it?
If there were any inconsistencies
in the survivors' statements
or if no corpses were found at the scene.
we would be suspicious of you.
What?
By the way.
although this is just our speculation...
Hunter Sung Jinwoo.
Please tell me.
have you experienced a Reawakening?
Reawakening...
A hunter's ability is set
at the time of awakening
and will not change in their lifetime.
However. a very few hunters
will experience a second awakening.
They'll surpass their limits
and become A-rank or S-rank hunters.
Did I also...
This is a magic power detector.
Please place your hand on this.
If what the survivors said is true
and there were magic beasts
that killed people with ease.
no low-rank hunters would survive.
However. those magic beasts
disappeared without a trace.
Only A-rank. no...
Only S-rank hunters
would be capable of that.
That's why we suspect that he had
undergone a second awakening.
What does it say?
If I had a second awakening.
what rank would I be?
It seems...
We should apologize.
Even an E-rank hunter
would have at least 70...
He's basically like an ordinary man.
The dungeon has disappeared
and can no longer be investigated.
How on earth did he survive?
What...
Got me excited for nothing.
By the way.
don't those people care about this thing?
Is it because
only I can see it?
This isn't a touch-sensitive screen?
I saw this too at that time...
Jinah.
You should take better care of yourself.
I'm terribly worried!
Sorry...
Why is everyone else okay?
Why do you get injured all the time?
I was really worried.
I actually thought
of leaving her and dying...
Why are you smiling?
If you risk your life again.
I'll drop out of school and work.
so you won't have to be a hunter.
I got it. sorry.
By the way. Jinah. can you see this?
See what?
Sorry. it's nothing.
A question.
There are unread messages in games. right?
Games?
How can I read them?
Maybe you should get your brain checked.
Jinah. didn't you used to play
video games?
I did.
Just open the message box.
Open the message box?
Why did you bring up games?
Well. I have nothing to do
in the hospital.
I think it mentioned
"player" or something.
Looks like you are fine.
I'll be going then.
Song-Yi. sorry to keep you waiting.
"This system is designed to assist
the development of the player."
"Failure to comply with the system
may result in a penalty."
"The rewards have been delivered."
I don't understand this at all.
"Daily quest.
strength training has arrived."
Confirm.
"Push-ups. sit-ups. squats. running."
"Failure to complete the daily quest
will result in an appropriate penalty"?
What is this?
Let's not joke about that.
I'm hospitalized. so I don't have
the strength to do those things.
What is going on?
That hunter. Sung Jinwoo.
shows no signs of a second awakening.
President Go.
I see.
We're lucky that there was
no Dungeon Break.
But this incident
is still too puzzling.
Yes.
This case is different
from all previous ones.
Although there are still many
mysteries in the dungeon...
I understand.
Let's list this case as special.
File it in the database.
and we will discuss it later.
Understood.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hunter Cha.
I'd like you to be the instructor
for the next B-rank raid mission.
I'll be the instructor?
This raid mission will also be
an on-site practice for the rookies.
We'll appreciate your efforts.
But I don't feel suited
for being an instructor.
You just need to fight as usual.
They will learn from watching you.
That's how influential your strength is.
Although our Hunters Guild is one
of the five major guilds in the country.
we're still not strong enough worldwide.
The rank of hunters is set.
but combat abilities
can be improved through practice.
in order to face the moment
that is approaching.
A portal again?
Why did a portal appear here?
Haven't the hunters arrived yet?
I hope they can hurry up
and get rid of it.
An earthquake?
A desert?
What is going on?
Am I dreaming?
Wasn't I just in the ward?
No way...
What?
What's wrong?
The patient in this ward...
How many ones are there?
Still two hours left...
Did you find him?
No.
- I will check the ward again.
- Okay.
I think he should still be
in the hospital...
I can't... carry on anymore...
"Penalty...
Quest..."
Mr. Sung?
Mr. Sung. are you all right?
Hmm.
I am recovering very well.
I should be able to go home soon.
That's great.
I was really worried about you.
After you're discharged.
you owe me a cup of Chagall black tea.
Okay. I got it.
Okay. let's go.
Eh. you want me on a raid mission?
Yes.
A D-rank portal appeared
at Hapjeong lately.
All Guilds are short on manpower.
Of course. it's not mandatory
for you to go.
I'm aware of your current situation.
I'm sorry...
No. don't worry about it.
Ah. right.
I heard that Hunter Sung Jinwoo
had woken up.
Really?
So you are fine. Jinwoo.
That's great...
Look. he's running again.
Geez...
It's been like this every day
since he woke up.
Jinwoo...
Unlike ordinary people.
hunters can recover quickly.
But he said he wants to get more strength.
I told him not to push himself.
but he didn't listen.
He just recovered from a severe injury.
It's quite worrying.
Today is the fourth day since I woke up.
I've figured out a few things.
First of all.
this thing in front of me
isn't my illusion.
If I complete the daily quest.
I can get three rewards.
Recovery.
My fatigue is instantly gone.
Next is Ability Points.
I can allocate the points
to the abilities I want to improve.
Strength is the most important.
When the ability points increase.
I become stronger.
I do feel that my strength has increased.
There are also skills
and the item warehouse.
I'm witnessing these amazing things.
It's like a game.
The last daily quest reward
is this random box.
What will it be today?
A key?
I always get useless things
like a pen or a band-aid.
"Instance dungeon"?
What is that?
It should also be part
of the strength training.
Next is today's update on the portal.
New D-rank portals emerged
at locations on the screen.
C-rank portals in the eastern and central
regions are currently being dealt with.
The B-rank portal appeared days ago
at the harbor area
and is expected to be dealt with
by the Hunters Guild soon.
Traffic control will be implemented
during this period.
Residents nearby and commuters.
please pay extra attention.
Understood. I'll head back
to headquarters first.
Sorry.
Mom!
Mom. wake up!
What's wrong?
Mom is...
I can't wake her up.
Eternal Slumber...
Also known as "The Final Sleep."
It's a condition that arose
after the portals appeared.
It afflicts one in tens of thousands.
Rumors say it's due to
prolonged exposure to Mana.
But still. with the current
medical technology.
we can only do so much to keep her alive.
Hey. kid!
Don't dawdle!
Yes.
Congratulations.
you have qualified as a hunter.
We look forward
to your future contributions.
It's great. Jinah.
Now I can pay mom's medical bills.
But. isn't that dangerous?
No worries.
I've got this.
What are you doing?
Just stay in the corner.
An E-rank hunter is just a hindrance.
Let me make this clear.
Those who don't work
don't get to share the spoils.
Sorry. I couldn't help...
Ability Points.
Strength.
I've got all my gear.
All preparations are done.
I'm confident in my ability to escape.
If it gets dangerous like last time.
I'll just run with all my might.
Is it...
The entrance is blocked?
I see...
This is a different dimension.
Instance dungeons differ
from regular dungeons.
I've never been in one.
but I guess it should be similar
to a Red Portal.
What a headache.
I thought if things went wrong.
at least I could run away.
Now there's nowhere to go.
"Teleportation stone"?
What now?
I can't get out unless I defeat the boss?
I couldn't even defeat
an E-rank magic beast.
Now I have to conquer this dungeon alone?
It's too difficult for me.
Do I really have to fight the boss
without a team?
But...
I have no choice.
What should I do...
I'm losing my confidence.
Beasts! And three ones at a time!
I killed it.
I really became stronger...
Wolf.
I can feel it...
It's much stronger
than the goblins just now.
My legs...
I can't move.
What's going on...
Is it because of fear?
I thought it hadn't left
a scar in my heart.
Damn it.
There is no healer.
If I get injured. it's all over.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today